casualcollective.com 2017-05-25

# The Casual Collective - Social Gaming & Casual Networking

Welcome to The Casual Collective. The Casual Collective, respects the privacy rights of our users and is committed to protecting the information collected on its application and website. We have adopted this privacy policy to explain how we collect, store and use the information collected. All of these policies and disclosures are collectively referred to in this document as the "Privacy Policy".

**What does this Privacy Policy apply to?**

**How does The Casual Collective collect information?**

**What information does The Casual Collective collect?**

**A Special Note about our Message Boards**

**What happens if I refuse to provide my personal information?**

**Does The Casual Collective use cookies, track IP Addresses or use other passive means to collect information?**

**Who is collecting my information and how will it be used?**

**With whom does The Casual Collective share my personal information?**

**How you can control the collection, use, and/or display of data by The Casual Collective**

**How do I access, change, or delete my personal information?**

**What is The Casual Collective's policy regarding links to other sites?**

**What safeguards does The Casual Collective use to protect my personal information?**

**How do I ask a question or file a complaint?**

**What does this Privacy Policy apply to?**

This Privacy Policy applies solely to The Casual Collective located at www.casualcollective.com. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other web sites (even those that are referenced on, or linked to through, The Casual Collective) or websites maintained by other companies or organizations.

By using and submitting personal information The Casual Collective, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use The Casual Collective. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the change on The Casual Collective website and, if necessary, give you additional choices regarding such change. Your continued use of The Casual Collective will signify your acceptance of these changes.

**How does The Casual Collective collect information?**

In connection with its games, The Casual Collective collects information from you in three ways.

  1. When you play certain Casual Collective games (such Minions or Splitter 2), information about your game play may be collected and transmitted to The Casual Collective. The Casual Collective may use such information in connection with The Casual Collective as set forth in this Privacy Policy whether or not you register on or use The Casual Collective.

  1. You may choose to voluntarily provide us with various personal information and non-personal information through your use of The Casual Collective.

  3. We may automatically collect certain non-personal information from you in connection with your use of The Casual Collective.

**What information does The Casual Collective collect?**

The Casual Collective may receive information regarding your game play and usage without any additional notice to you or actions taken by you. The Casual Collective will not receive personal information such as your name and address but may receive other information such as your email address, game played, game score, performance, Internet Protocol (IP) address or other information and statistics regarding your usage of the games. 

When you register and use The Casual Collective, you may voluntarily provide, and The Casual Collective may collect, personal and non-personal information in the form of website registration data (name, email, etc), and other data necessary to fulfill your requests, participate in game-specific services, and participate in special services such as newsletter subscriptions, "email this page" features, technical support, demos, downloads, polls, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions. The Casual Collective may also passively collect certain information about your use of The Casual Collective, such as the pages you visit and the features you use (see "Cookies" below).

**A Special Note about our Message Boards and Chat Rooms**   
Whenever you give out personal information in public areas such as on a message board, that information can be collected and used by other people. While we strive to protect those who wish to participate in these services, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you post in these areas.

**E-mail Correspondence**

We may collect personal information about you, such as your e-mail address or any other personal data contained in the registration process. We will never sell your email address; we only use the information for the purpose of promotions about Casual Collective games. If you do not with to receive emails, you have the ability to unsubscribe.

**What happens if I refuse to provide my personal information?**

Your refusal to submit personal information may limit your ability to participate in some activities on The Casual Collective. However, as described above, The Casual Collective may nonetheless post game play boards that contain certain information as a result of your use of the games.

**Does The Casual Collective use cookies, track IP Addresses or use other passive means to collect information?**

The Casual Collective may use cookies and similar tracking devices. A "cookie" is a small bit of record-keeping information that websites often store on a user's computer. Cookies generally do not include people's names, e-mail addresses, or other information that is personally identifiable; they are typically used to quickly identify a user's computer and to "remember" things about the user's visit (such as the user's use of various features on the service). You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer; however, disabling cookies may affect your ability to use certain portions of The Casual Collective.

The Casual Collective may also keep track of your Internet Protocol (IP) and computer MAC addresses for various reasons. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. A computer MAC address identifies one specific piece of hardware.

Other information that may be passively collected by Casual Collective includes log files that record website activity, including how many "hits" a particular web page is getting (a.k.a. "navigational data"). These entries are generated anonymously and enable Casual Collective to assess overall online activity and a user's browsing habits, track interest in advertised sales, and troubleshoot technical concerns. We also use the log file entries for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the online services we provide you.

**Who is collecting my information and how will it be used?**

When you submit information on The Casual Collective, or information is automatically collected as described in this Privacy Policy, The Casual Collective uses the submitted information to send you promotional materials, to provide you with access to our services, to fulfill product orders, and to respond to questions or technical problems. We also use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the products and services we provide you and to better meet your needs. 

**With whom does The Casual Collective share my personal information?**

The Casual Collective does not share your personal information with any third parties. In the event we offer services or promotions where your information is separately collected and used according to the privacy policy of a third-party, we will inform you of that at the time of collection and you may elect not to participate in the service or promotion We also may share your information with third parties as required by law enforcement or other government officials in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose you or us to legal liability. In addition, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event involving all or a portion of The Casual Collective, Casual Collective's customer information may be transferred to our successor or assign.

Notwithstanding anything else herein, we may partner with third party advertisers who may (themselves or through their partners) place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. These cookies enable more customized ads, content or services to be provided to you. To trigger these cookies, we may pass an encrypted or "hashed" (non-human readable) identifier corresponding to your email address to a Web advertising partner, who may place a cookie on your computer. No personally identifiable information is on, or is connected to, these cookies. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to <http://www.privacychoice.org/choose>. 

**How you can control the collection, use, and/or display of data by The Casual Collective**

If you do not want The Casual Collective to send you communications such as newsletters or promotional offers, you may opt-out from receiving these communications by contacting us here: [http://casualcollective.us1.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=5eced92a8fcc78097e537a7be&id=b4ac30a70c&e=&c=7708bb8d4b](http://casualcollective.us1.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=5eced92a8fcc78097e537a7be&id=b4ac30a70c&e=&c=7708bb8d4b)

Or emailing us: updates@casualcollective.com

By regular mail at The Casual Collective, Attn: Privacy Policy, 100 California Street, Floor 4, San Francisco, California 94111. 

**How do I access, change, or delete my personal information?**

If for any reason you wish to view, correct or delete the personal information collected about you, please go here: [http://casualcollective.us1.list-manage.com/profile?u=5eced92a8fcc78097e537a7be&id=b4ac30a70c](http://casualcollective.us1.list-manage.com/profile?u=5eced92a8fcc78097e537a7be&id=b4ac30a70c).

**What is The Casual Collective's policy regarding links to other sites?**

You should be aware that while you are on The Casual Collective you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. Because we cannot guarantee that the privacy policies of these websites meet our high standards, we recommend reading the privacy policy of the website you link to before you submit any of your personal information.

**What safeguards does The Casual Collective use to protect my personal information?**

To protect your personal information, The Casual Collective maintains reasonable safeguards to attempt to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided. The Casual Collective has security measures in place designed to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Personal information collected by The Casual Collective is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public (e.g., locked rooms). To prevent unauthorized electronic access to personal information, The Casual Collective maintains information collected online behind a firewall-protected server and uses SSL encryption for purchases made through our online store. However, no system can be 100% secure and there is the possibility that despite our reasonable efforts, there could be unauthorized access to your information. By using our services, you assume this risk.

**How do I ask a question or file a complaint?**

Any questions or complaints about this Online Privacy Statement can be resolved by contacting our Privacy Policy Administrator via email at [updates@casualcollective.com](mailto:privacypolicy@take2games.com); or, by regular mail at The Casual Collective, Attn: Privacy Policy, 100 California Street, Floor 4, San Francisco, California 94111.
